mykeyport.com 2017-04-15

# Privacy

## PRIVACY POLICY

We value your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal information. Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.

If you have questions about our Privacy Policy, please send them to us by email to [helpdesk@mykeyport.com](mailto:helpdesk@mykeyport.com) or write to us at the following address: Keyport Inc., Attention: Privacy Dept., 3155 W. Tompkins Ave., Las Vegas, NV 89103.  

### Types of Information

When you visit our website you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and website use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our website.

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. 

### Personal Information

Any personal information that you provide us on our website is stored in our secure web server and our other internal systems. When you purchase or register on our website, we collect your personal information. This may include, but is not limited to, your name, billing and shipping address, phone number, email address, and credit card information. We may use your information in the following ways:  

· To process and fulfill your order (e.g. sending you emails to apprise you of your order and shipment status)  
To send you an email to you confirming the registration of your customer account  
· To communicate with you about our products, services and promotions unless you have previously specified that you do not wish to receive this information  
· To help us learn more about your shopping needs and preferences  
· To enhance your shopping experience  
· To analyze customer trends and maintain statistics  
· To contact you if necessary

### Viewing, Updating, or Modifying Personal Information

We will provide you with access to the personal information you provided to Keyport by allowing you to view, update or correct your online registration information. In order to protect your privacy, Keyport takes steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the private information or enabling you to make corrections. We will accomplish this through the use of passwords and personal data. If we cannot provide access within the 30-day period, we will tell you when we will provide access. In the unlikely event that we cannot provide you access to this information, we will explain why we cannot do so. To request access to your personally identifying information, please login to your online account or contact us by email at [helpdesk@mykeyport.com](mailto:helpdesk@mykeyport.com) or by writing us at the following address: Keyport Inc., Attention: Privacy Dept., 3155 W. Tompkins Ave., Las Vegas, NV 89103.

### Mailing List

We have exciting news to share with you from time to time. We encourage you to joining our mailing list in order to receive the latest information about our products, services, promotions, and special orders. At any point, you may opt to remove your email address from our mailing list. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at [helpdesk@mykeyport.com](mailto:helpdesk@mykeyport.com).

### Web Site Use Information

Similar to other commercial websites, Keyport utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" and web server logs to collect information about how our website is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, pages viewed, time spent on our site, and the website visited just before and just after visiting our website.

### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small text file that a Web site can place on your computer's hard drive in order, for example, to collect information about your activities on the site or to make it easier to use certain site functions. The cookie transmits this information back to the Web site's computer. Many users do not know that "cookies" are being placed on their computers when they visit Web sites. If you want to know when this happens, or prevent it from happening, you can set your browser to warn you when a Web site attempts to place a "cookie" on your computer.  

Cookies allow you to place an order on our website and allow us to enhance and personalize your online surfing and shopping experience. For example, we use cookies to:  

· Remember the items in your shopping basket  
· Recognize you when you return to our website  
· Analyze visitor behavior

### Web Site Analytics

We also use cookies to analyze how visitors, in the aggregate, use our website, in order to make our website as useful as possible for them. We do not use cookies to collect or store personally identifiable information. We may also use a third party web analytics service provider that uses cookies and web beacons to help us analyze how users use this website and the effectiveness of our marketing search terms. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website (including, without limitation, your IP address) may be transmitted to and stored by this service provider. They may use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of our website and compiling aggregated reports for us. The information collected by our service provider and provided to us is not personally identifiable.

### Information Automatically Collected by Our Website

Our servers automatically collect certain non-personally identifying information, such as your computer's IP address, the type of browser in use, and pages viewed, when you visit our Sites. We use this information to understand how visitors navigate through our website, to enhance your experience while using our website, and to make the materials we post as valuable to visitors as possible. We do not link this information to personally identifiable information.

### Third Parties

We may choose to work with other companies who use tracking technologies to serve ads on our behalf across the internet. These companies may collect non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our website and your interaction with our communications, including advertising.

We may also enter into alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number and email for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. In connection with alliances, partnerships or arrangements, we may also provide certain information to third parties if we have determined that the information will be used in a responsible manner by a responsible third party. For example, some of our partners operate stores or provide services on our site, while others power offerings developed by us for your use. We also use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email and processing credit card payments. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our partners and other third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with business activities. As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.  

### Certain Disclosures

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or affiliated parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our site, the users of our site, and/or our affiliated parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our site, us, or third parties.

### Linked Websites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

### Consent

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

### Updates to Privacy Information

Please review the site periodically to see any updates to the information provided here. This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 18, 2013.
